<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="hotelCatalog.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE hotelCatalog SYSTEM "hotelCatalog.dtd" [
    <!NOTATION PNG SYSTEM "image/png">
    <!NOTATION JPG SYSTEM "image/jpeg">
	<!ENTITY festa_sofia_hotel SYSTEM "images/Festa_sofia_hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY festa_sofia_room SYSTEM "images/Festa_sofia_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY festa_borovets_hotel SYSTEM "images/Festa_borovets_hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY festa_borovets_room SYSTEM "images/Festa_borovets_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY royal_castle_hotel SYSTEM "images/Royal_castle_hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY royal_castle_room SYSTEM "images/Royal_castle_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY marinela_hotel SYSTEM "images/Marinela-hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY marinela_room SYSTEM "images/Marinela-room.jpg"  NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY chaika_hotel SYSTEM "images/Chaika_hotel.png"  NDATA PNG>
	<!ENTITY chaika_room SYSTEM "images/Chaika_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY rila_borovets_hotel SYSTEM "images/Rila_borovets_hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY rila_borovets_room SYSTEM "images/Rila_borovets_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY perla_beach_hotel SYSTEM "images/Perla_beach_hotel.jpg" NDATA JPG>
	<!ENTITY perla_beach_room SYSTEM "images/Perla_beach_room.jpg" NDATA JPG>
]>

<hotelCatalog>

 <hotel hotelChainID="Festa" regionID="SOF" type="Conference" stars="4">
  <name>Festa Sofia</name>
  <address>Bulgaria Blvd. 83, 1404 Manastirski Livadi, Sofia</address>
  <description>
   Located 200 meters from Mall Bulgaria and the tram stop, Festa Sofia hotel offers elegant rooms with free Wi-Fi and satellite TV.
   It features a wellness center and beauty salon, as well as 2 restaurants, 3 bars, and 4 conference halls. The spa center includes a sauna and steam bath.
   Guests can stay fit in the fitness center or enjoy massage and aromatherapy treatments. There is also a hair salon on site. 
   Restaurant Festa serves local and international cuisine in a secluded atmosphere. The Mezzanine bar offers sophisticated drinks and desserts.
   The lobby bar serves a variety of coffee specialties. Sahara Hookah Bar offers its guests exquisite varieties of tobacco and a wonderful selection of drinks.
   All rooms at Festa Sofia hotel have a panoramic view of the city or Vitosha. They are equipped with air conditioning and a safe. 
   The private bathrooms have a bathtub. The hotel is located in a modern business area, 18 km from Sofia International Airport and 5 km from the city center.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="festa_sofia_hotel" />
   <photo src="festa_sofia_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Private Parking, Free WiFi, Airport Shuttle, Fitness Center, Family Rooms, Non-Smoking Rooms, 2 Restaurants,
   24-Hour Reception, Bar, Good Breakfast
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="single">
	<price>120</price>
	<capacity>1</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="double">
	<price>150</price>
	<capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
	<price>200</price>
	<capacity>3</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="Festa" regionID="BOR" type="Botique" stars="5">
  <name>Festa Winter Borovets</name>
  <address>2010 Borovets, Borovets</address>
  <description>
   The luxurious 5-star Festa Winter Palace is located at the foot of Rila in Borovets, just 100 meters from the ski slopes and the gondola lift. 
   It offers an indoor pool. The large relaxation center with a pool, sauna, steam bath, fitness facilities, and a wide range of massages is a wonderful place 
   to relax after a day outdoors in the mountains. The spacious rooms and suites feature antique-style furniture, and a balcony overlooking the mountain.
   The hotel has 2 restaurants and 2 bars serving gourmet cuisine and select drinks. Free WiFi is available throughout Festa Winter Palace.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="festa_borovets_hotel" />
   <photo src="festa_borovets_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Indoor Pool, Private Parking, Free WiFi, Family Rooms, Fitness Center, Restaurant, Ski Services, Coffee/Tea Maker in All Rooms,
   Bar, Good Breakfast
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="single">
	<price>600</price>
	<capacity>1</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="double">
	<price>650</price>
	<capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
	<price>1100</price>
	<capacity>3</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="Vic" regionID="BRG" type="Resort" stars="5">
  <name>Royal Castle Design &amp; SPA</name>
  <address>8259 Elenite, Bulgaria</address>
  <description>
   Royal Castle Design &amp; SPA is located in a closed and peaceful complex in the resort village of Elenite. The hotel offers an outdoor seasonal pool with free sun loungers
   and umbrellas, as well as access to the beach. During the summer season, the hotel hosts various live shows, concerts, and parties with DJs. The hotel offers elegant 
   designer rooms, all equipped with a flat-screen TV, minibar, and a private balcony. Guests also have access to 4 VIP apartments with boutique designer furnishings, 
   their own SPA area, and additional amenities for a truly luxurious experience. During the summer season, hotel guests have free access to the "Atlantis" aqua park. 
   Available for guests are an indoor pool, sauna, SPA center, as well as a fitness room and a squash court.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="royal_castle_hotel" />
   <photo src="royal_castle_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Sea View, Outdoor and Indoor Pool, Private Parking, Free WiFi, 24-Hour Reception, Fitness Center, 2 Restaurants,
   Spa and Wellness, Family Rooms, Bar, Good Breakfast
  </features>
   <rooms>
	<room type="double">
	 <price>475</price>
	 <capacity>2</capacity>
	</room>
	<room type="suite">
	 <price>1050</price>
	 <capacity>4</capacity>
	</room>
   </rooms>
  </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="Vic" regionID="SOF" type="Conference" stars="5">
  <name>Hotel Marinela Sofia</name>
  <address>James Bourchier Blvd. 100, Lozenets, 1407 Sofia</address>
  <description>
    Hotel Marinela Sofia has an entirely new design and is located 20 minutes by car from Sofia Airport. It offers an indoor pool, 6 restaurants, 4 bars, a fitness club,
	and a picturesque view of the city and the mountain. The unique Japanese garden is a wonderful place for relaxation or meetings. Guests can dine at the Panorama restaurant 
	while enjoying the city view and spend a great evening at the Megami club. The hotel has a large ballroom and a conference hall, plus 13 meeting rooms and a remarkable 
	top-floor hall at Hotel Marinela with a unique view of Sofia. Each room is equipped with air conditioning, heating system, flat-screen TV, free WiFi, and a modern 
	entertainment system with video and music.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="marinela_hotel" />
   <photo src="marinela_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Airport Transfer, Private Parking, Indoor Pool, Free WiFi, Mountain View, 6 Restaurants, Spa and Wellness,
   Family Rooms, Bar, Good Breakfast
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="single">
    <price>175</price>
    <capacity>1</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="double">
    <price>230</price>
    <capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
    <price>2200</price>
    <capacity>4</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="Vic" regionID="BRG" type="Resort" stars="3">
  <name>Chaika Beach Resort</name>
  <address>Sunny Beach, 8240 Sunny Beach</address>
  <description>
   Chaika Beach Resort is located in the northern part of Sunny Beach, right on the beachfront. It is divided into three buildings, some of which offer a panoramic view of the sea.
   The hotel has direct access to the beach, 2 outdoor pools, and several restaurants and bars. All-inclusive light offers include a main restaurant with a variety of 
   delicious dishes, a lobby bar, and a pool bar with umbrellas and sun loungers. Guests can enjoy top-notch summer cocktails or beer at the Irish Bar. All rooms are equipped 
   with air conditioning, a TV, and free WiFi.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="chaika_hotel" />
   <photo src="chaika_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Sea View, Private Parking, 2 Pools, Free WiFi, Large Outdoor Garden, Restaurant, Bar, Family Rooms,
   24-Hour Reception, Good Breakfast
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="double">
    <price>150</price>
    <capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
    <price>200</price>
    <capacity>4</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="BT" regionID="BOR" type="Resort" stars="4">
  <name>Hotel Rila Borovets</name>
  <address>Borovets, 2010 Borovets</address>
  <description>
   Rila Hotel Borovets is located in the heart of the first mountain resort in the Balkans - Borovets, 70 km away from Sofia. Rila Hotel Borovets is situated at the end of
   the ski slopes, just 200 meters from the gondola lift. It offers a SPA center, various restaurants, and entertainment clubs. Private parking and free WiFi are provided.
   The conference center offers different options for organizing business and personal events. Guests can take advantage of free access to the SPA center, 
   which includes a 25-meter swimming pool, 2 hydro-massage tubs, a fitness center, thermal zones, and relaxation areas. The hotel offers relaxation opportunities 
   through outdoor and indoor sports and entertainment activities. Equipment rental and skiing or snowboarding lessons are also available.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="rila_borovets_hotel" />
   <photo src="rila_borovets_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Mountain View, Private Parking, Indoor Pool, Close to Ski Slopes, Airport Transfer, 3 Restaurants, Bar,
   Family Rooms, Spa and Wellness Center, Fitness Center
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="single">
    <price>300</price>
    <capacity>1</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="double">
    <price>330</price>
	<capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
    <price>550</price>
    <capacity>4</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>

 <hotel hotelChainID="BT" regionID="BRG" type="Resort" stars="4">
  <name>Perla Beach Club</name>
  <address>18 Georgi Kondolov St., 8180 Center, Primorsko</address>
  <description>
   Perla Beach Hotel overlooks the Black Sea in the town of Primorsko. The hotel is located right next to the beach and offers 3 swimming pools, massage procedures, 
   and a sauna. All guest rooms feature air conditioning, a private balcony, and cable TV. Some accommodations have sea views. The spacious hotel restaurant is open all day 
   and offers local and international specialties. Perla Beach Hotel also has a lobby bar, a poolside bar, and barbecue facilities. Guests can take advantage of various sports 
   facilities, including a tennis court, volleyball court, and fitness center.
  </description>
  <photos>
   <photo src="perla_beach_hotel" />
   <photo src="perla_beach_room" />
  </photos>
  <features>
   Sea View, Outdoor Pool, Airport Transfer, Free WiFi, Restaurant, Family Rooms, Non-Smoking Rooms, Bar,
   Good Breakfast
  </features>
  <rooms>
   <room type="double">
    <price>170</price>
    <capacity>2</capacity>
   </room>
   <room type="suite">
    <price>185</price>
    <capacity>3</capacity>
   </room>
  </rooms>
 </hotel>
	
 <hotelChain hotelChainID="Vic">
  <name>Victoria Group Hotels and Resorts</name>
  <description>
   Their portfolio consists of 11 hotels categorized as 3, 4, and 5 stars, over 500 holiday villas, and multifunctional halls located in various destinations. 
   Their hotels impress with unconventional and unique designs. Their advantage lies in their locations—by the sea, in the center of Sofia, or near some of the best ski slopes!
   Their vacation hotels offer All-Inclusive accommodation with included meals, drinks, and services, ensuring a worry-free vacation! The Victoria Group Hotels and Resorts 
   portfolio includes some of the most elegant and luxurious wedding venues in Bulgaria — from the heavenly beaches of Elenite to the city lights of Sofia.
  </description>
  <numberOfHotels>10</numberOfHotels>
 </hotelChain>

 <hotelChain hotelChainID="BT">
  <name>BT Collection</name>
  <description>
   BT Collection is a collection of luxury hotels and complexes situated in some of the most beautiful places in Bulgaria—Black Sea Coast, Borovets, and Arbanasi.
   The hotels combine an elegant ambiance, modern design, luxury, and high-quality service, symbolizing tourism in Bulgaria. The BT Collection offers SPA facilities,
   relaxation, delicious food, and entertainment, suitable for family vacations as well as business trips and conferences.
  </description>
  <numberOfHotels>7</numberOfHotels>
 </hotelChain>

 <hotelChain hotelChainID="Festa">
  <name>Festa Hotels</name>
  <description>
   Festa Hotels is a hotel chain established in 2003, known for its consistently high service quality and personalized approach to every guest. Thanks to their attractive locations,
   the chain's hotels offer various options for summer seaside relaxation, winter ski holidays, business travel, and a wide range of rejuvenating SPA and balneotherapy procedures.
   For sea vacation enthusiasts, Festa's collection includes three hotels in two of the most popular destinations on the Bulgarian Black Sea—Nessebar and Pomorie.
   Guests can also enjoy mountain ski vacations at their hotels in Borovets, as well as urban business trips with the offerings of Festa Sofia Hotel, located in a tranquil spot
   in the capital.
  </description>
  <numberOfHotels>7</numberOfHotels>
 </hotelChain>

 <region regionID="SOF">
  <name>Sofia</name>
  <description>
   Sofia is the capital and the largest city in Bulgaria. The population is around 1.3 million people. Sofia is located in the central part of Western Bulgaria. 
   It serves as the main administrative, industrial, transportation, cultural, and educational center of the country. The transportation system in the capital is highly developed.
   In Sofia, you can find:
   - Numerous educational institutions, including the oldest and largest higher education institution in Bulgaria - Sofia University "St. Kliment Ohridski," 
     as well as the Bulgarian Academy of Sciences and the National Library "Sts. Cyril and Methodius."
   - Temples of major world religions, with around 200 functioning Orthodox churches and chapels and over 40 monasteries, one of which is the memorial temple "Alexander Nevsky."
   - Theatres and opera houses, including the Ivan Vazov National Theatre and the Sofia Opera and Ballet.
   - Museums and galleries such as the National Historical Museum, the National Ethnographic Museum, and the National Art Gallery.
   - Monuments from various historical periods.
   - Concert halls, the largest of which is Arena Sofia with up to 15,000 seats.
   - Vasil Levski Stadium, the largest stadium in the country with a capacity of 44,000 people.
   - Other notable places include the National Palace of Culture, the two oldest and well-known bridges in Sofia - the Eagle Bridge and the Lion Bridge, 
   the largest park in Sofia - Borisova Gradina, and the Sofia Zoo.
  </description>
  <sights>
   Sofia University "St. Kliment Ohridski", Bulgarian Academy of Sciences, National Library "Sts. Cyril and Methodius",
   memorial temple "Alexander Nevsky", National Theatre "Ivan Vazov", Sofia Opera and Ballet, National Historical Museum,
   National Ethnographic Museum, National Art Gallery, Arena Sofia, Vasil Levski Stadium, National Palace of Culture,
   Eagle Bridge, Lion Bridge, Borisova Gradina, Sofia Zoo
  </sights>
  <transports>
   <transport type="trainStation">
    <name>Central Railway Station Sofia</name>
    <link>https://www.centralnaavtogara.bg</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="busStation">
    <name>Central Bus Station Sofia</name>
    <link>https://www.centralnaavtogara.bg</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="airport">
    <name>Sofia Airport</name>
    <link>https://www.sofiaairport.bg</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="publicTransport">
    <name>Urban Mobility Center</name>
    <link>https://www.sofiatraffic.bg</link>
   </transport>
  </transports>
 </region>

 <region regionID="BRG">
  <name>Burgas</name>  
  <description>
   Burgas is the largest city in Southeastern Bulgaria and the second largest on the Bulgarian Black Sea coast. The population is around 210,000 residents.
   Burgas is the most important cultural, economic, transportation, administrative, tourist, and educational center in Southeastern Bulgaria and is considered 
   the most romantic city in Bulgaria with its small streets in the center, old houses, and the Sea Garden. Over 40% of mass tourism in the country takes place 
   in the Burgas region. Festivals, concerts, and exhibitions form a rich program of cultural events that embody the unique spirit of Burgas.
   In Burgas, you can find:
   - Museums, theaters, and operas, such as the Ethnographic Museum and the Burgas Opera.
   - Temples and monasteries, including the cathedral temple "Sts. Cyril and Methodius."
   - Concert halls, the largest being Arena Burgas with up to 15,000 seats.
   - "St. Anastasia" island.
   - The Sea Garden with the Sea Casino and the Burgas Bridge.
   Near Burgas, you can find:
   - The Strandzha Mountain region.
   - The ancient Thracian sanctuary Beglik Tash.
   - Numerous resort towns, some of which are Nesebar, the only Bulgarian city - part of UNESCO, the medieval town of Apollonia (today Sozopol), Sunny Beach, Pomorie, and Primorsko.
   - Campsites, including "Gradina," "Zlatna Ribka," "Smokinya," and "Kavatsite."
  </description>
  <sights>
   Ethnographic Museum, Burgas Opera, cathedral temple "Sts. Cyril and Methodius", Arena Burgas, "St. Anastasia" island,
   Sea Garden, Strandzha Mountain, Beglik Tash, resort town Nesebar, resort town Sozopol, resort town Sunny Beach,
   resort town Pomorie, resort town Primorsko, campsite "Gradina", campsite "Zlatna Ribka", campsite "Smokinya",
   campsite "Kavatsite"
  </sights>
  <transports>
   <transport type="trainStation">
    <name>South Bus Station</name>
    <link>https://www.bdz.bg</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="busStation">
    <name>South Bus Station</name>
    <link>https://burgasbus.info</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="airport">
    <name>Burgas Airport</name>
    <link>https://burgas-airport.bg</link>
   </transport>
   <transport type="publicTransport">
    <name>BurgasBus</name>
	<link>https://burgasbus.info</link>
   </transport>
  </transports>
 </region>

 <region regionID="BOR">
  <name>Borovets</name>  
  <description>
   Borovets (formerly known as Chamkoria until 1942) is the first resort in Bulgaria and the primary tourist center in the Samokov municipality with international significance,
   offering opportunities for practicing all kinds of winter sports. Borovets is the closest winter resort to Sofia and is located in the Rila Mountain. The resort has 26 hotels
   with accommodation for 98,000 guests, along with an excellent network of ski slopes and lifts, diverse restaurants, and bars. Borovets hosts various ski competitions and 
   also offers opportunities for mountain biking, rock climbing, and mountaineering.
   Near Borovets, you can find:
   - The highest peak not only in Bulgaria but also in the entire Balkan Peninsula - Mount Musala in the Rila Mountain, standing at 2,925 meters.
   - Rila Monastery - one of the most significant cultural monuments in Bulgaria, included in UNESCO's World Heritage List.
   - The summer royal residence Tsarska Bistritsa.
   - Tsari Mali Grad - an archaeological site located in the village of Belchin.
   - The Seven Rila Lakes - one of the largest natural landmarks not only in Bulgaria but also in the Balkan Peninsula.
   - The eco-trail Beli Iskar.
   - Lift stations: Yastrebets, Martinovi Baraki Express, Sitnyakovo, Yastrebets Express, Markudjik 2.
   - Ski lifts: Sitnyakovo, Rila, Iglika, Rotata, Markudjik 0, Markudjik 1, Markudjik 3.
  </description>
  <sights>
   Mount Musala, Rila Monastery, Tsarska Bistritsa, Tsari Mali Grad, Seven Rila Lakes, eco-trail Beli Iskar,
   lift station Yastrebets, lift station Martinovi Baraki Express, lift station Sitnyakovo, lift station Yastrebets Express,
   lift station Markudjik 2, ski lift Sitnyakovo, ski lift Rila, ski lift Iglika, ski lift Rotata, ski lift Markudjik 0,
   ski lift Markudjik 1, ski lift Markudjik 3
  </sights>
  <transports>
   <transport type="busStation">
    <name>Samokov Bus Station</name>
    <link>http://avtogara-samokov.eu</link>
   </transport>
  </transports>
 </region>
</hotelCatalog>